♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll reset it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
I’ve got a bad feeling about this.
Are you almost done Aelita?
Yes, almost.
Watch out,
another squadron of Mantas is headed your way!
Done, the controls are all yours Jeremie.
Great!
Here come your vehicles.
Okay guys, the passage is open.
So, anything good?
No. I wouldn’t call it good.
Huh?
More like amazing!
With this, I bet I can crack the code of Franz Hopper’s diary!
Way cool.
The only problem is I’m gonna need a supercomputer--
--to process such a large amount of data.
I’ll have to activate a tower or two.
Uh, that didn’t go very well last time,
XANA hates it when we play with his toys.
I know. But we don’t have a choice.
Right, can we go eat now?
It’s mashed potatoes today!
You can have mine.
I better stay here to prepare the mission.
That way, you can set out right after lunch.
Um, Jeremie’s not coming,
he said I could have his portion too Rosa.
Yeah!
With everything you put away,
I just don’t understand how you can be so scrawny.
I am not scrawny, I’m svelte.
So come on, Ulrich, stop holding out on us.
What’s your overall average?
73 for the term.
For me, I got 75.
I beat ya.
Only because you made up some points in art class.
What about Aelita,
what’s your grade point average?
95.2
Um, but it’s only because of math.
Yes, but still you must have gotten--
--good grades in all of your classes.
It’s great, especially since you’re not really…
Uh...
Uh, I mean…
Don’t worry,
I know very well I’m not really human.
Still, sometimes I get a strange feeling as if…
As if I’ve already lived here. Weird, huh?
That’s just the magical Odd-effect.
You know, you see me once and you--
--feel like you’ve known me forever.
Hey magic Odd-effect you know you got--
--some mashed potatoes right on your face.
(LAUGHTER)
No way!
Something wrong?
Not really.
Some girl wants me to meet her in the woods.
You kidding?
Who?
The number’s masked.
No doubt about it, it’s just another girl who’s--
--just too shy to admit she’s crazy about me.
You know Odd,
your love life is like something out of a soap opera.
Oh yeah? And yours is real simple?
An activated tower, oh boy. That’s all I needed.
(PHONE RINGING)
Yeah, Jeremie?
Huh? Okay, we’re on our way.
Activated tower. You call Yumi, I’ll tell Odd.
Uh, are you there? It’s me Odd!
What do you mean, ”SOS XANA”, no way!
Not now!
Who’s there? No,
No.
No!
NO!
Where’s Odd?
I sent him a text message,
but he was supposed to be meeting some sort of mystery girl.
A girl? What girl?
Mystery girls don’t leave their names.
I hope he won’t he won’t be much longer.
Not only we have to decode Franz Hopper’s notes,
but now we have to deactivate the tower as well.
Okay, let’s go.
Come on, Odd, pick up!
(PHONE RINGS)
He’s not answering, forget him for now.
He’ll meet you later.
Transfer, Ulrich.
Transfer, Aelita.
Transfer, Yumi.
Scanner, Ulrich.
Scanner, Yumi.
Scanner, Aelita.
Virtualization.
Here I am Jeremie.
Not a minute too soon.
I’ve been trying to call you.
I was busy.
Huh? Well get ready, I’ll launch the procedure.
Transfer, Odd.
Scanner, Odd.
Virtualization.
What?
What’s going on here?
Odd?
Everything’s okay, I’m on Lyoko.
There was a bug during the transfer. Oh, no way!
The tower has just deactivated itself.
Are you sure?
Yeah, the superscan shows all clear.
As if XANA has called off his attack.
Well, that’s one less thing for us to worry about, right?
Right Odd?
Right.
What’s up with him?
Is he sulking or something?
Maybe his rendezvous didn’t go well.
Here are your rides,
please remember we have a diary to decode.
I’ve chosen the tower at 72 degrees south,
and 55 degrees west.
There it is!
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
As soon as I activate the tower,
start the decoding process.
(HUMMING CONTINUES)
I’m ready, Jeremie.
Ok, I’m activating the tower…
Now!
Yeah! It’s working!
The deconing of the data’s underway, Jeremie,
but it might take some time.
No problem, whenever Xana leave us in peace,
everything’s cool.
Uh oh, I spoke too soon.
Watch out, Xana’s creatures heading your way.
Where from? We can’t see anything.
Huh?
There!
Wow, Xana’s pulled out the big guns.
Hey!
Huh?
Jeremie, Xana’s taken over Odd!
What?
Yes, I’m sure of it.
I don’t know how Xana did it.
I do, it’s not the real Odd.
What?
It’s one of Xana’s creatures,
a polymorphing spectre.
But where’s the real Odd then?
Hey! Is anybody there?
Yohoo!
Help!
Talk about a tailgater,
worse than Sissi.
Ulrich, it’s a trap, he’s trying to lead you away from the tower.
But why?
Jeremie, what’s going on?
Is there a problem?
Oh man.
Xana’s trying to gain control of the tower,
abort the mission!
Stop the decoding,
and come back to Earth.
Ok.
Yumi, where are you?
In the woods.
But it’s like trying to find a needle in a haystack.
Wait, while I was hacking into the network,
I managed to locate the emergency telephone closest to Odd’s phone.
You can do that?
Ofcourse I can.
If odd still has his cell on him,
then he’s in the north-east corner of the woods.
That’s near the Hermitage, I’m off.
Jeremie, we’ve got a problem,
I can’t stop the decoding program,
it’s taking up too many resources,
it’s out of my control now.
Bad news, if Xana manages to take control of the tower now,
he’ll be able to get into the restricted access part of the supercomputer.
I could lose all the data in Franz Hopper’s diary.
No to mention everything you’ve programed in yourself.
Our combat gear, the vehicles, the transfer codes,
and my materialization program.
This is a nightmare.
Ulrich!
Xana’s about to take control of the tower, you have to stop it.
Uh, right, ok, but how?
You have to isolate the tower, try to cut the cables, hurry!
You’re wasting your time, Xana, Odd has never beaten me yet.
Uh well yeah, ok uh, that changes things.
Help!
(PHONE RINGS)
Odd?
Odd!
Xana’s going to do it,
Aelita. Is there anything new?
There’s no way to stop the process,
everything’s buggy.
Help!
Hey, you’re not so bad there, Xana.
Whoa! Full of surprises, huh?
Hey, no fair!
It figures,
at least I don’t have to climb anymore.
Well I guess you can say I’m really--
--up to my neck in trouble this time.
Xana’s about to take over!
Ulrich, what are you doing?
I just got one last little thing to take care of.
All done Jeremie.
Make it fast, now!
Ulrich!
Odd?
Odd!
Yumi, I’m here!
Yumi!
Odd?
Odd!
Xana is about to steal all my data!
We’re done for!
Hey!
What’s going on?
Aelita?
I don’t get it, it looks like Xana has lost control of the tower.
Franz Hopper!
Franz Hopper’s helping us!
What’s going on on your side?
The decoding program is going full speed.
No girls have ever kept me waiting that long.
(LAUGHTER)
Huh?
Amazing.
Yumi.
I’ve got Odd, how about you?
We’re decoding Franz Hopper’s diary.
Franz Hopper was the creator of Xana.
In his diary, he wrote everything that--
--happened during the creation of Lyoko.
Everything.
That means you’ll be able to find the antivirus!
Yeah, it does, but there’s something more.
What?
Come on, spit it out.
Well, before Franz Hopper virtualized himself on Lyoko,
and before being taken prisoner by Xana, he lived here on Earth.
We already knew that.
Yes, but what you didn’t know was--
--that he had a child, a little girl.
Really? Well what became of her?
He virtualized her on Lyoko at the same time as himself.
And?
Did she fall victim to Xana, too?
No, she stayed on Lyoko.
But that’s impossible, if Hopper’s daughter--
--were on Lyoko, I would have definitely known, I--
I’m-- Not...
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS